We  treat  time  like  a  bottomless  bank  account
until  the  statement  finally  bounces.  Brownie  wearer,  a
nurse  who  spent  years  sitting  with  the  people
in  their  final  peaks  found  that  nobody,  not
even  a  single  person,  wish  they  would  have
spent  more  time  in  office  to  earn  an
extra  zero.  Instead  they  talk  about  the  stolen
movement.  They  didn't  say,  I  wish  I  earned
more  money.  They  said,  I  wish  I  allowed
myself  to  feel  happy.  Think  about  it,  a
man  postponed  his  vacation  for  next  year.  A
woman  delay  is  calling  her  parents  because  she
was  too  busy.  A  couple  saying  one  thing,
once  the  thing  settled  down,  we  will  live.
But  life  doesn't  wait  for  permission.  In  hospital,
tomorrow  is  luxury  that  no  one  can  afford.
Don't  wait  for  diagnosis  to  start  your  life.
Money  can  buy  you  a  bed  in  hospital,
but  it  can't  buy  back  the  Tuesday  afternoons.
You  spend  stressing  over  the  things  that  doesn't
matter.  Happiness  isn't  a  reward  for  your  hard
work.  It's  an  engine  that  should  power  it.
Tag  someone  who  really  needs  to  hear  this
today  and  put  the  phone  down  to  go
live  your  life  and  follow  for  more.